[{"answer": "Did you give blood", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Blood.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "In case of what", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Tomorrow evening, sure", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Blood.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Do I know anyone?", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "So, she didn't appreciate the erotic qualities of the salted cured meats", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Blood.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Natural? Sex is about love between a man and a woman, not a man and a sandwich", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Hey, what are you doing here? I thought you were bab", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Blood.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Oh no, where's the blood?  It's in here isn't it", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "It's Jel", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Blood.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "This is tomato juice, look..", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Will you calm down. I took all my blood down to my friend's. He let me put it in his meat freezer", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Blood.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Oh yeah yeah, my friend he came by and made more of those pudding skin singles. They're delicious", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "So, my blood is not enough. Would you like a kidney too, because I'll give it to you? I'll rip it out right here and stack it on the table", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Blood.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "No no no, I don't have time right now. I'll catch you tonight, we'll do sort of an all over kind of thing, all right?", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Hello?", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Blood.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "my friend called you", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "my friend called, he told that you were in a hospital", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Blood.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "He calls every week. Are you all right", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "He calls every week. Are you all right", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Blood.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "He says he's fine", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Her grandparent passed away five years ago", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Blood.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "She's that place citizen, I have seen her passport", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "That's because it's underwater", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Blood.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Is it", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "There's something wrong with your car. It's dripping something on my feet. Some kind of red liquid", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Blood.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Blood!!", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "my friend, it was overheating. You should take better care of that thing", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Blood.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "You didn't get the blood from me", "qsentId": 28}]